字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
我看见你了
I saw you
你是说你在监视我
You mean you were spying on me
不，我只是路过
No. I was just passing
莎拉，我在城镇的另一边工作，你怎么刚刚路过？
Sarah, I work on the opposite side of town How were you just passing?
你为什么不能告诉我真相？
Why can't you just tell me the truth?
真相？行
The truth? Okay
- 你确定？ - 是的…不，呃
- Are you sure?  - Yes. No. Erm
我见过一个人
I've met someone
有人吗？我以为我是你的人
Someone? I thought I was your someone
听着，我只是需要一些空间，想想事情
Listen, I just need some space, think about things
但是我们刚刚搬进来
But we've only just moved in
听着，我会过来收集我的东西
Look, I'll come and collect my stuff
当你平静下来的时候
when you've calmed down
冷静？哦，我非常平静
Calm? Oh, I am perfectly calm
看到了吗？
See?
哦！
Oh!
祝福你
Bless you
你在这里，亲爱的
There you are, darling
这个死去的尸体
this body who died
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
是的，谢谢
Yes, thanks
我应该认为她，你知道，二十岁
I should think she's, you know, 20
是
Yes
天气变得有点热
It's getting a bit hot
这么年轻，太棒了
So young, wonderful
这是美味的蛋糕
This is delicious cake
看起来也是
Looks it, too
我想她大概三十三岁了
I think she's probably 33
你到底去了哪里？遗憾的
Where on Earth have you been? Sorry
你错过了服务
You missed the service
奶奶的朋友邓肯不得不帮你读书
Granny's friend Duncan had to do your reading
他忘了带眼镜，所以一点意义都没有
He'd forgotten his glasses, so none of it made any sense at all
哦，我很抱歉
Oh, I am so sorry
你好
Hi
莎拉
Sarah
你把衣服前后穿好了吗？
Have you got your dress on back to front?
呃，是的，现在是时候了
Er. Yeah. It's very now
来让自己变得有用
Come and make yourself useful
这群人正在喝茶
This lot are inhaling the tea
啊！那在这里做什么？看起来很可笑
Ugh! What's that doing here? It looks ridiculous
哦…它在奶奶的愿望清单上
Oh... It was on Granny's list of wishes
嗯
Hmm
至少他准时
At least he was on time
你能告诉我洗手间在哪里吗？
Can you tell me where the loo is?
是的，当然，亲爱的
Yes, of course, dear
疯狂的
Bonkers
爸爸
Dad
布丁
Pudding
你没事吧？是的，亲爱的
Are you okay? Yes, darling
无限远，超越莎拉阿姨！
To infinity and beyond Auntie Sarah!
不，厕所不是那样的
No, the loo's not that way
哦，这就是你们都藏的地方
Oh, this is where you're all hiding
我们真的应该整天看电视吗？
Should we really be watching telly, today of all days?
来吧，卡罗琳，他们在外面太无聊了
Come on, Caroline. It's so boring for them out there
总之，这对他们的单身阿姨来说很好
Anyway, it's nice for their single auntie
拥抱侄女和侄子
to have an armful of niece and nephew
妈妈对爸爸说，当你真的老了
Mummy said to Daddy that when you're really old,
你将全靠你自己
you'll be all on your own
呃，扎卡里，你介意来吗
Erm, Zachary, would you mind just coming
当你死了，他们只会发现你的骨架
And when you die, all they'll find will be your skeleton
还有很多非常胖的猫
and lots and lots of really fat cats
请你注意一下好吗？
May I have your attention, please?
虽然我母亲留下了正式遗嘱
Although my mother left a formal will,
她还想让我读出她个人愿望的清单
she also wanted me to read out a list of her personal wishes
她希望下面的人去她家
She would like the following people to go to her home
并选择一个项目让他们想起她
and to choose an item to remind them of her
哦！来了
Oh! Here goes
阿奇博尔德，我的会计师哦
Archibald, my accountant Oh
安吉拉
Angela
你的伙计不能请一天假吗？
Couldn't your chap get the day off work?
啊，我和我的兄弟已经不在了
Ah. My chap and I are no more
哦，莎拉，不是另一个
Oh, Sarah Not another one
我们要对你做什么？
What are we going to do with you?
你了解我，爱他们，离开他们
You know me, love 'em and leave 'em
嗯，这可能是最好的，我不是很喜欢
Well, it's probably for the best I wasn't very taken
我希望当时人们会说些什么
I wish people would say something at the time
而不是等到那个人走了
rather than waiting till the person's gone
我不想干涉
Well, I didn't want to interfere
嗯，这是第一次
Hmm, that's a first
哦，呃，顺便说一下，我得到了那份工作
Oh. Er, by the way, I got that job
我下学期开始学十一年级英语
I start next term Head of year 11 English
达内曼综合公司
Daneman Comprehensive
真遗憾你从法学院退学了
Such a shame you dropped out of law school
去参加教师培训
to go to teacher training
现在你姐姐是律师，妻子和母亲
Now your sister's a barrister And a wife and a mother
难道我们不知道吗？
Don't we just know it?
你呢
And you
有所有好看的外表吗？嗯
Got all the good looks? Hmm
那只该死的狗
That blasted dog
鲁伯特，我理发师的朋友
Rupert, my hairdresser's friend
别这样
Stop that
哦，我的天
Oh, my goodness
最后，嗯，莎拉，我留下了我最珍贵的财产
And finally, um, to Sarah, I leave my most treasured possession
哦，格拉夫，真可爱，她一直知道我喜欢那枚费伯奇胸针
Oh, Granfoos, how lovely. She always knew I loved that Faberge brooch
我亲爱的帕特里克
My beloved Patrick
什么？
What?
- 你确定？ - 是的，是
- Are you sure?  - Yes. Yes
她给了你帕特里克
She's bequeathed you Patrick,
帕特里克，她的哈巴狗
Patrick, her pug
多甜蜜不不
How sweet No. No
她补充道，他们会很好的相处，完全地
She's added, They'll be very good for each other. Absolutely
- 我不太了解你，但我更喜欢威士忌  - 不，我们不会的
- I don't know about you lot, but I rather fancy a whisky.  - No, we won't
我们是地狱里的一对，爸爸
We're a match made in hell. Dad
爸爸？
Dad?
不不不不！其他全锁其他方式
No, no, no, no. Other full lock Other way
就这样，就这样，就这样
That's it. That's it That's it
快回来，没错，回来吧
Come on back now. That's right Come on back
太好了，非常好，停下来
Excellent. Jolly good And stop
好吧，我知道我在做什么不，不，停下来
All right. I know what I'm doing No, no, stop
停下！停下！仅仅
Stop! Stop! Just
她在想什么？
What was she thinking?
我们能抓到他吗？
Can we have him?
不，是的
No Yes
为什么不呢？你妈妈过敏
Why not? Your mother's allergic
是的，如果我们真的养了一只狗，那一定是一只可卡波狗
Yeah, if we ever did get a dog, it would have to be a cockapoo
那我们能买一个吗？不
Can we get one of them, then? No
为什么不呢？
Why not?
因为我有太多事情要做，这将是另一件值得担心的事情
Because I have too much to do, and it'd be one more thing to worry about
抱怨什么？
Complain about What?
没什么你不能拥有他吗？
Nothing Can't you have him?
哦，不，亲爱的，不
Oh. No, darling, no
可怜的白雪公主需要几周时间才能康复
Poor Snowy's gonna take weeks to recover
如果我们找到他，嗯
If we ever find him Hmm
求你了？
Please?
对不起，布丁
I'm sorry, pudding
奶奶在想什么？她知道我住在公寓里
What was Granny thinking? She knows I live in a flat
我可以补充一下，租约上说不准养宠物
And, might I just add, the lease says no pets.
房东会发疯的
The landlord would go ape
我在一周内开始一份新工作，我会出去一整天
And I start a new job in a week I'm gonna be out all day
和…我不喜欢狗
And... And I don't like dogs
我不想要狗
I don't want a dog
你们不能带他去吗？
Can't one of you take him?
哦，太棒了
Oh, brilliant
什么？
What?
得了
Stop it
别看着我，好吗？这不是我的主意
Stop looking at me, okay? It wasn't my idea
拜拜
Bye Bye
来吧，小家伙，该走了
Come on, little ones. Time to go
安全驾驶，亲爱的
Drive safely, darling
好吧，你真的吓坏我了
Okay, you're really freaking me out now
你不能看看窗外吗？很好
Can't you look out the window? It's nice
有一座城堡和一切
There's a castle and everything
慢炖兔子？
Slow-cooked rabbit ragout?
三块九毛九？
￡3.99?
人们很容易受骗，我敢打赌都是一样的东西
People are so gullible I bet it's all the same stuff
把它放回去
Put it back
给我看看你从哪里得到的
Show me where you got it from
哦，坚持住对不起，那不是我的
Oh. Hang on Sorry. That's not mine
不知道这是怎么进来的
Don't know how that got in there
我怀疑一个小家伙有一张可爱的压扁的脸
I suspect a little person with an adorable squashed face
把它放在那里，这样妈妈以后会有一些好吃的
put it in there so Mummy'd have some treats for later
嗯，他可以吃一些妈妈提供的巧克力
Well, he can have some of Mummy's not inconsiderable supply of chocolate instead
你不知道巧克力对他们有毒吗？
Don't you know chocolate's poisonous for them?
真的吗？哦，对妈妈来说尤其如此
Really? Oh, well All the more for Mummy
好吧，你现在吓坏我了，是我开车还是
Okay, you're freaking me out now Is it my driving or is
哦
Oh
停止
Stop
好吧，不要引起你的注意
Okay, don't draw attention to yourself
你好
Hi
租金周四到期
Rent's due Thursday
祝你晚上愉快
Have a nice evening
对，首先，我们要摆脱这套可笑的服装
Right, first thing, we're getting out of this ridiculous outfit
第二，我要在Facebook上和可能在Tinder上公开你的身份
Secondly, I'm putting you up for grabs on Facebook and possibly Tinder
我的意思是，如果有邻居抓到我们，上帝会帮助我们的
I mean, God help us if any of the neighbors catch us
我说真的，帕特里克
I mean it, Patrick
一声咕哝、低吼或在错误的地方吠叫
One grunt, growl or bark in the wrong place
我们都将在里士满公园吃兔肉
and we'll both be in Richmond Park eating rabbit ragout
我知道这听起来不错，但不会
I know that sounds nice, but it won't be
帕特里克
Patrick
现在是早上六点
It's 6:00 in the morning
正确
Right
我们开始吧
Here we go
继续，享受
Go on. Enjoy
来吧，我以为你绝望了
Come on. I thought you were desperate
现在你让我想去
Now you're making me want to go
哦，我的上帝！呃，你在这里做什么？
Oh, my God! Erm What are you doing here?
哦，对不起，我没想到会有客人
Oh, I'm sorry I wasn't expecting company
啊，我明白了，另一个犯法者
Ah. Another law-breaker, I see
好吧，你必须小心，你永远不知道谁会告发你
Well, you have to keep an eye out. You never know who might turn you in
名字？
Name?
莎拉·杰西卡·罗斯玛丽·弗朗西斯
Sarah Jessica Rosemary Francis
不，你的狗
No, your dog
帕特里克
Oh, Patrick
他真的不是我的狗
He's not really my dog
我祖母把他留给了我
My grandmother left him to me
我真的需要给他找个家
I really need to find him a home
你不能这么做他是遗产
You can't do that He's a bequest
你不能把他卖给第一个出价人
You can't just pack him off to the first bidder
我是一名教师，我是说，我不能带他一起去
I'm a teacher. I mean, I can't take him with me
我不能把他一个人留在这里
And I can't leave him here on his own
我相信你会找到办法的
Well, I'm sure you'll find a way
谢谢
Thanks
多好的女孩
What a good girl
你来这儿没多久
You haven't been here long
刚搬进来
Just moved in
这里
Here
哦，不，谢谢你
Oh. No, thanks Not for you
这是给狗的，你必须捡起帕特里克的便便
It's for the dog. You've got to pick up Patrick's poo
是的，对吧
Yes, right
我是西莉亚
I'm Celia,
这是温迪
and this is Wendy
呃，我们最好离开
Erm. We'd better be off
是的，再见
Yep. See you around
或者没有，眨眼，眨眼
Or not. Wink, wink
帕特里克，这太恶心了
Patrick, that's gross
我知道这是个坏主意
I knew this was a bad idea
我告诉他们了，我告诉他们这行不通，但是他们会听我的吗？
I told them. I told them it wouldn't work, but would they listen to me?
老实说，还有一件事，你就要被解雇了，我受够了
Honestly, one more thing and you're off to the pound. I have had it
电子战！哦
Ew! Oh
哦
Oh
哦，真恶心
Oh, that is disgusting
你怎么了？
What is the matter with you?
我是说，都是食物
I mean, it's all food
如果你饿了，你会吃的
If you were hungry, you would eat it
我不能这么做
I can't be doing
啊！
Ugh!
帕特里克
Patrick
帕特里克？帕特里克？
Patrick? Patrick?
帕特里克！
Patrick!
我刚刚换了床
I've just changed that bed
不不
No. No
我知道奶奶过去惯于宠坏你
I know Granny used to spoil you rotten
但是当你在这里的时候，你处于一个新的政权之下
But while you're here, you're under a new regime
冰箱不准放
The fridge is out of bounds
我不是因为拿走它们而出名
Not that I'm known for taking them,
但是在公园散步可能会增强老年人的食欲
but a walk in the park may sharpen the old appetite
运气好的话，你会筋疲力尽的
With any luck, you'll wear yourself out
帕特里克脚跟
Patrick, heel
帕特里克
Patrick
脚跟，脚后跟
Heel. Heel
帕特里克
Patrick
把事情控制住
Get that thing under control
- 对不起，帕特里克  - 你在干什么？
- Sorry. Patrick.  - What are you doing?
帕特里克
Patrick
帕特里克，来这里
Patrick. Come here
帕特里克，我是认真的，我说真的，帕特里克过来
Patrick, I mean it. I mean it, Patrick Come here
哦，上帝，帕特里克！
Oh, God. Patrick!
来吧，好孩子
Come. Good boy
好吧，留下来，好孩子，留下来，好孩子
Okay. Stay. Good boy Stay. Good boy
停下！
Stop!
哦，不！
Oh, no!
为什么，奶奶？为什么？
Why, Grandma? Why?
我尽可能来看你
I came to see you whenever I could
我从未打断过你，尽管我已经听过你的故事二十次了
I never interrupted, even though I'd heard your stories 20 times
我做错了什么？
What did I do wrong?
你有机会吗？
Yours by any chance?
差不多，哦，可怜的狗
Sort of. Oh, wretched dog
谢谢你抓住他，没关系
Thanks for catching him That's okay
哦，上帝，多么大的灾难
Oh, God. What a disaster
我已经和祖母的哈巴狗在一起了
I've been landed with my grandmother's pug
我甚至不想要一只我讨厌的狗
I don't even want a dog I hate dogs
你不讨厌狗
You don't hate dogs
不，也许我只是讨厌这个
No. Maybe I just hate this one
你抓他多久了？
How long have you got him for?
呃，我不知道，他九岁了，健康状况非常好
Er, I don't know. He's nine and in annoyingly good health
如果你幸运的话，也许五年
Maybe five years, then, if you're lucky
五年？
Five years?
我会因为持械抢劫得到更少的报酬
I'd get less for armed robbery
哦，这只是出牙的问题
Oh, it's just teething problems
你只需要了解对方
You just need to get to know each other,
形成一种理解，就像任何关系
form an understanding It's like any relationship
真的吗？
Really?
他会期待我捡起他的内裤
He'll be expecting me to pick up his underpants
几周后
in a few weeks' time
好吧，你们会互相信任，好吧
Well, you'll get to trust each other and, well,
你会想知道没有他你会怎样生活
you'll wonder how you ever lived without him
你和我有非常不同的感情经历
You and I have very different relationship experiences
但是我可以试试看
But I could give it a go
不要轻易放弃他
Don't give up on him too easily
他是个可爱的小家伙，真的
He's quite a cute little fella, really
呵
Ooh
我能帮你回到停车场吗？
Can I give you a hand back to the car park?
谢谢你，我可以给它一两分钟
Thank you. I might give it a minute or two
以防其他步行者在我回到车上之前用石头打我
In case the other walkers stone me before I get back to the car
暂时让他领先
Keep him on the lead for the time being
他是个男人，他对明确的指示做出了回应
He's a man. He responds to clear instruction
哦，我会的，谢谢你
Oh. I will. Thank you
好吧，再见？
Well, see you around?
是
Yeah
大多数狗带回一只兔子，帕特里克，做得好
Most dogs bring back a rabbit Well done, Patrick
几周后，他会期待我帮他捡起内裤
In a few weeks' time, he'll be expecting me to pick up his underpants.
不，帕特里克
No, Patrick
家具上没有，好吗？
Not on the furniture, okay?
这是新政权的一部分
It's part of the new regime
明天开学第一天
First day of school tomorrow
我要你留在这里，尽情娱乐，直到我回来，好吗？
I want you to stay here and entertain yourself until I get back, okay?
祝我好运
And wish me luck
哦
Oh
谢谢你的支持
Thanks for the support
不
No
不不不不！
No, no, no, no
不不不！不不不！
No, no, no, no, no
我第一天就迟到了
My first day and I'm late
呵
Ooh
好吧，我来了，但是快点
Okay, I'm coming, but be quick
哦！
Oh!
帕特里克，你吃了什么？
Patrick, what have you eaten?
哦，上帝
Oh, God
哦，真恶心
Oh, that is disgusting
哦，上帝，哦，上帝
Oh, God. Oh, God
很高兴它从两端出来
Well, glad it's coming out of both ends
不不
No. No
不，不，帕特里克
No, no, Patrick
哦，不
Oh, no
帕特里克
Patrick
帕特里克，就这样，过来来吧，进步
Patrick, that's it. Come here Come on. Come along
来吧，好孩子帕特里克，来吧
Come on. Good boy Patrick, come on
好孩子，来吧，帕特里克
Good boy Come on. Patrick
帕特里克，帕特里克
Patrick. Patrick
好孩子，是啊，好孩子，开始
Good boy. Yeah, good boy. Come on
这是什么？来吧，帕特里克
What's this? Come on Come on, Patrick
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
开始
Come on
帕特里克！
Patrick!
帕特里克，马上来
Patrick, get here right now
帕特里克，我真的很生气！
Patrick, I am really very angry!
如果你现在不到这里
And if you don't get here right now,
我第一天就要失业了
I am gonna lose my job on my first day
我必须住在桥下的纸板箱里
And I'm gonna have to live in a cardboard box under a bridge
没有人会爱我
and no one's ever gonna love me,
我的生活就要结束了
and my life is gonna be over
抓住了
Gotcha
现在，我将在四点半回来
Now, I'll be back at 4: 30
我不在的时候，请不要碰任何东西
Please don't touch anything while I'm gone
跑吧
And run
对不起，对不起
Sorry, excuse me
对不起，走开，请下车
Excuse me, off. Off, please
早上好！
Good morning!
行
Okay
总是管用，早上好，请坐
Always works. Good morning Please take your seats
我是弗朗西斯小姐，你的新英语老师
I'm Miss Francis, your new English teacher
好吧，如果你能向我介绍一下自己，请
Okay. If you could just introduce yourselves to me, please
好吧，那你怎么拼写呢？
Okay. And how do you spell that?
在这么短的时间内，我只能得到她
She was all I could get at such short notice
我打赌你会和弗朗西斯小姐有纪律问题
Well, I'm betting you'll have disciplinary problems with Miss Francis
哦，啊！欢迎
Oh. Ah! Well, welcome
谢谢你
Thank you
嗨，不要以为我们见过我是莎拉·弗朗西斯
Hi. Don't think we've met I'm Sarah Francis
我主修纪律
I major in discipline
好吧，好吧，我一会儿再来找你
Okay, right. Well, I'll catch you later
大错特错，大错特错
Big mistake. Huge mistake
嗨，你一定是莎拉，新来的女孩
Hi. You must be Sarah, the new girl
嗨，是的，我是贝基，开始
Hi. Yeah I'm Becky. Come on
不要让这些阻碍了你
Don't let this lot put you off
请原谅
If you'll excuse me
别介意老彼得斯他不喜欢改变
Don't mind old Peters He doesn't like change
或者英语老师或者金发女郎
Or English teachers Or blondes
让开，莫林，这是莎拉
Budge up, Maureen This is Sarah
你好，她教十一年级英语
Hello. She teaches year 11 English
你想要一块摇滚蛋糕吗？
Would you like a rock cake?
哦，谢谢
Oh. Thanks
你们班做的啊
Your class made those Ah
是的，线索在名字里
Yep. Clue's in the name
让我们希望他们的英语好一点
Let's hope their English is a bit better
我打赌你会想知道我教什么
I bet you're wondering what I teach
啊，让我猜猜，经济学？
Ah. Let me guess. Economics?
关闭，我是游戏老师之一
Close. I'm one of the games teachers
我想这都是莱卡
Thought so It's all the Lycra
我正在为慈善组织一次有趣的跑步
And I'm organizing a fun run for charity
哦？我在想
Oh? And I was wondering
如果你能说服你的班级跑步的话？
if maybe you could persuade your class to run?
我该怎么做？
And how would I do that?
通过进入你自己
By entering yourself
哦
Oh
哦，我真的很抱歉，我不是跑步者，从来没有
Oh, I'm really sorry. I'm not a runner, never have been
我也喜欢游泳，我做了所有正确的动作，只是哪儿也不去
I'm the same with swimming. I do all the right actions, I just don't go anywhere
总之，我很难说服我的班级
Anyway, just had huge difficulty trying to persuade my class
读简·爱的第一页，所以
to read page one of Jane Eyre, so,
我不喜欢玩得开心
I don't fancy my chances with a fun run
只有五公里
It's only five kilometers
那是英里，我的意思是，那实际上是一场马拉松
That's miles. I mean, that's practically a marathon
不，不是
No, it's not
你穿过公园，上山，然后回到学校
You go through the park, up the hill and then back into school
因此…你刚才是说上山吗？
So... Did you just say up the hill?
我希望你知道，当人们对我说不的时候，我会将此视为谈判的开始
I hope you know that when people say no to me, I treat that as start of negotiations
嗯，我想你在这里见过你的对手
Well, I think you've met your match here
哦
Oh
哦，没关系
Oh. Doesn't matter
是啊，对不起，谢谢
Yeah, sorry. Thanks
没关系，我会找到一个牙齿好的人
It's all right. I'll find someone with good teeth
是
Yeah
你想再来一块蛋糕吗？
Would you like another cake?
亲爱的，我回来了
Darling, I'm home
哦，不
Oh, no
伙计，你毁了我的生活
You, mate, are ruining my life
没有你很难，但是有了你，这是不可能的
It was hard enough without you, but with you, it's impossible
你不能再这样了
Well, you can't do that again
进来吧
Do come in
每当一只流浪儿路过，他都会尖叫着把这个地方推倒
Every time a stray animal wandered by, he screamed the place down
我担心会有一封信
I fear there's going to be a letter
我能给你拿杯茶吗？
Can I get you a tea?
不，我建议你带他去散步
No. And I suggest you take him for a walk
当你离开一整天的狗时，你就是这样做的
That's what you do when you leave a dog all day
是的，当然我正要去
Yeah, of course I was just about to
听着，我会整理一些东西，但是明天你能让他来吗？
Look, I will get something sorted, but could you have him tomorrow?
不，只是为了明天
No Just for tomorrow
不，他表现得太差劲了
No, he's so badly behaved
但是他和同伴在一起会更好
But he'd be so much better with company
你真的会帮我
You'd be really helping me out
看看情况如何？求你了？请
Just see how it goes? Please? Please
好吧，就为了明天，但是你必须整理一下自己
Well, just for tomorrow, but you have to sort yourself out
别担心，我会的，谢谢你，西莉亚，谢谢你
Don't worry, I will. Thank you, Celia Thank you
我欠你的是的，你欠我的
I owe you Yes, you do
如果你明天不守规矩
If you don't behave tomorrow,
你真的要去狗家
you really are going to the dog home
来
Coming
嗨，我真的不确定这一点
Hi. I'm really not sure about this
温迪和我过着非常平静的生活
Wendy and I lead a very quiet life
哦，这只是为了今天，帕特里克表现得非常好
Oh, it's just for today. And Patrick is very well behaved
我奶奶非常严格
My granny was very strict
她至少和我们在一起
She was with us, at least
我四点半回来
I'll be back at 4:30
现在，说声谢谢，并提议洗碗
Now, say thank you and offer to do the washing-up
开始
Come on
妈妈要抛弃你了
Mummy's abandoning you
进来吧
In you come
主人公简·爱
Jane Eyre, the protagonist
谢谢你
Thank you
它从来不是狗它永远是主人
It's never the dog It's always the owner
那边有场打斗
There's a fight over there
哦，哦，下车，得了
Oh. Oh. Get off. Stop it
你们应该为自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourselves
哦，不
Oh, no
你做了什么？哦，亲爱的
What have you done? Oh, my darling
我一直知道你有点奇怪
I always knew you were a little strange
再也不会了哦，对不起
Never again Oh. I'm sorry
这是他的衣领对吗
Here's his collar Right
再见，我真的很抱歉
Goodbye I'm really sorry
嗨
Hi Hi
哦哦
Oh Oh
对不起，不
Sorry Sorry, no
哦，上帝，哦，哈
Oh, God. Ooh, ha
对不起
Sorry Sorry
这一定是我们的错
It's bound to be our fault Yeah
很快就要宣布我们订婚了
Be announcing our engagement soon
他很可爱
He's cute
可爱？停留
Cute? Stick around
我能问问吗，当你养狗的时候，你在想什么？
Can I just ask, when you got a dog, what were you thinking?
我喜欢，一点陪伴让自己保持健康
I like 'em. Bit of companionship Keep myself fit
像这样走路、思考的时刻
Moments like this Walking, contemplating
是啊，所以你永远也不想抓住它的喉咙，然后把它推到英镑上去？
Yeah, so you never wanna grab it by the throat and march it off to the pound?
他摧毁了什么？
What's he destroyed?
哦，呃，我的生活
Oh. Erm, my life
哇，令人印象深刻的
Wow. Impressive
你和他在一起多久了？
How long have you had him?
太长了，这是我祖母的遗赠
Too long. It was a bequest from my grandmother
我希望至少有微波炉
I was hoping for the microwave at least
也许她有理由把他留给你
Maybe she had her reasons for leaving him with you
她九十二岁了，我不确定推理是她的强项
She was 92. I'm not sure reasoning was her strong point
嗯，我认为你应该坚持下去
Well, I think you should stick with it
为什么？
Why?
我不知道，不然你怎么能和一个完全陌生的人在公园里玩Twister呢？
I dunno. How else would you get to play Twister in a park with a complete stranger?
顺便说一下，我是本
Hmm I'm Ben, by the way
哦，莎拉嗨
Oh, Sarah Hi
呃，这是童子军
Er, this is Scout
杀死一只知更鸟
To Kill a Mockingbird
呃，精确地
Er. Precisely
啊
Ah
很高兴见到你我也很高兴见到你
Well, nice meeting you Nice to meet you, too
来吧，童子军，开始
Come on, Scout. Come on
嗯，我必须把它交给你，你是一个非常吸引人的宝贝
Hmm. I have to hand it to you, you are quite the babe magnet
哦，好吧，来吧
Oh, all right, come on
不过这只是今晚用的
This is just for tonight, though
帕特里克，我该怎么处置你？
Oh, Patrick, what am I gonna do with you?
别担心，我会想办法的
Don't worry, I'll think of something
好吧
Right, okay
我，呃，我能帮你吗？
Can I, er Can I help you?
嗨，呃，我是莎拉·弗朗西斯，新来的英语老师
Hi. Er, I'm Sarah Francis, the new English teacher
我想知道你和我是否能达成协议
I was wondering if you and I could come to an arrangement
你想要什么？
What do you want?
你能带这只狗吗？就为了今天
Could you take this dog? Just for today
不
No
我给你十英镑
I'll give you ￡10
- 四十  - 什么？
- ￡40  - What?
他会整天坐在你的房间里
He's just gonna be sitting in your room all day,
也许你会在午餐时间带他出去
and maybe you'd take him out at lunchtime
那是五十什么？
That's ￡50 What?
现在是六十岁了
Now it's ￡60
我们过夜怎么样
How about we have a sleepover
放学后去购物？
and a bit of shopping after school?
是
Yeah
没关系，小姐在这里
It'll be okay Miss is here
你没事吧？是
You okay? Yeah
不要帮我
Don't help me
是呃，是维克基，不是吗？
It's erm, it's Vikki, isn't it?
我来这里才一周，我也想哭
I've only been here a week and I feel like crying as well
你想谈谈吗？
Do you wanna talk about it?
不，你没事
No, you're all right
已经和学生建立了联系？多么现代
Bonding with the students already? How modern
我看到了
I saw that
我再问一次
I ask again,
罗切斯特先生是什么使他对简·爱如此完美？
what is it about Mr. Rochester that makes him so perfect for Jane Eyre?
她为什么不能摆脱他？
Why can't she get over him?
他的紧身裤？
His tight trousers?
你们怎么了？为什么你决定不把注意力放在你的练习本上？
What is it with you guys? Why are you determined not to focus on your set books?
这些是你的普通中等教育证书
These are your GCSEs
很无聊
It's boring
正确
Right
那…不爱
That... No Oi
小姐，我在看简爱的样子
Miss, I was looking at what Jane Eyre looked like
夏洛特没有提供照片
Charlotte hasn't provided pictures
好吧，好吧，让我们试试这个
Right, okay, let's try this
简的父母咬了那个大家伙死了，走了，好吗？
Jane's parents bite the big one Dead, gone, okay?
简被打包去和她姑姑住在一起
Jane is packed off to live with her aunt,
里德太太，在乡下，谁是一个合适的老家伙
Mrs. Reed, in the country, who is a right old bag
然后她拉了个眼罩，把她锁在房间里
And then she pulls a blinder, locks her in a room
和她死去叔叔的鬼魂在一起
with her dead uncle's ghost
哦！
Ooh!
是
Yeah
进来
Come in
这是你的狗
Here's your dog
听着，我们能在午餐时间谈这个吗？
Look, can we talk about this at lunchtime?
这只小狗吃了我的午餐
This little dog ate my lunch
哦！
Ooh!
我会在休息时间出去，给你买个三明治
I'll go out at break time and I'll buy you a sandwich
还有一包薯片和士力架
And a packet of crisps and a Snickers
窃笑？
A Snickers?
这正是我需要的
That is just what I need
怎么了，小姐？
What's the matter, miss?
巧克力对狗有毒
Chocolate's poisonous for dogs
哦，生病了，请生病
Oh, be sick. Please be sick
米奇，找到最近的兽医
Mikey, find the nearest vet
好吧，我正在疏通女孩们的厕所
Well, I was unblocking the girls' toilets
最近的兽医在主干道上，四百二十五号
The nearest vet's on the main road, 425
好吧，给他们打电话，告诉他们发生了什么
Okay, phone them and tell them what's happened
是的，是的，小姐，现在就走，快点，它会生病的
Yeah, yeah, miss, go now, quick Quick. It's gonna get sick
听着，我们会读第一章，直到下课
Look, we'll read chapter one until the bell goes
谢谢你，维克基
Thank you, Vikki
快，快，快，就这样
Quick, quick, quick That's it
把它装进去，你们很多人
Pack it in, you lot
你想当老师吗？那就去当老师吧
Do you wanna be a teacher? Go on then, be a teacher
这还不够好，戴安娜，你必须做得更好
It's not good enough, Diana You must do better
你知道这件事至少有两周了
You've known about this for at least two weeks
弗朗西斯小姐，那是你胳膊下的一只狗吗？
Miss Francis, is that a dog under your arm?
呃
Uh
是
Yes
众所周知，学校不允许养宠物
As you well know, pets are not allowed in school
我可以问一下你要带这条狗去哪里吗？
May I ask where you're taking this dog?
呃
Uh
去生物实验室做实验
To the biology lab for an experiment
青蛙用完了，是吗？
Run out of frogs, have they?
他刚刚吃了一块巧克力棒
He's just eaten a chocolate bar
我要带他去兽医诊所
I need to take him to the vet's
我可以问谁
And who, may I ask,
当你执行这项重要任务时，你在照顾你的班级吗？
is looking after your class while you perform this important task?
我让维克基·安德鲁斯负责，他们在读书
I've left Vikki Andrews in charge. They're reading
真的吗？是
Really? Yes
维克基是一个非常明智的年轻女性
Vikki is a very sensible young woman
对不起，怎么了？
Sorry, what is the matter?
你为什么反对我？
Why have you taken against me?
我没有反对你
I haven't taken against you
是的，你有
Yes, you have
自从我第一次来，你对我来说一直很可怕
Ever since I first arrived, you've been horrible to me
我是说，我对你做了什么？
I mean, what have I done to you?
对，说实话
Right, to be honest
是的，老实说
Yes, be honest
事实上，不太诚实，但请继续
Actually, not too honest, but go ahead
我喜欢一个能管教一个班级的老师
I like a teacher who can discipline a class,
让他们集中精力学习
get them focused and learning
你的类型只想和他们成为朋友
Your type just wants to be friends with them,
在这个学校，有了这个班级，这是行不通的
and with that class, in this school, that won't work
我的类型？你对我或我的教学方法一无所知
My type? You don't know anything about me or my teaching methods
我建议你现在就去我的教室
I suggest you go down to my classroom right now
看看我的学生能有多负责和专注
and see just how responsible and focused my students can be
现在，我要去兽医诊所，午餐时间我会回来
Now, I'm going to the vet's I'll be back at lunchtime
确保你是
Make sure you are
我只是说我会的
I just said I will be
托塞尔
Tosser
我听说了
I heard that
你是命中注定的
You were meant to
嗯
Hmm
两分钟
Two minutes
记住，记录是三分五秒
Now, remember, the record's three minutes and five seconds
好吧，谢谢你
Okay. Thank you
帕特里克·弗朗西斯
Patrick Francis
哦
Oh
哦，我明白了，你叫这只狗的名字“喔”，真可爱，嗯
Oh. I see. You call the dog's name Aw. That's cute. Um
呃，是的，帕特里克·弗朗西斯在这里
Er, yeah, Patrick Francis here
过来
Come on through
小猎鹿人怎么样了？
How is the little deer hunter?
他现在已经放弃了，他现在吃巧克力
He's given that up now. He's now the chocolate eater
你知道巧克力是
You do know that chocolate is
有毒，是啊，这是个错误
Poisonous, yeah It was a mistake
怎么样了？
So how's it going?
呃，一般来说还是和帕特里克一起？
Er, in general or with Patrick?
让我们从帕特里克开始
Let's start with Patrick
哦，呃…嗯，除了我给他放的食物，他什么都吃
Oh. Er... Well, he eats everything except the food I put down for him
呃…当我工作的时候，我已经没有人看他了
Erm... I'm running out of people to watch him while I'm at work
我期待着不可避免的驱逐通知
And I'm expecting the inevitable eviction notice
从我刚搬进的公寓
from my flat I've just moved into
因为他们有严格的禁止宠物的政策
because they have a strict no pets policy
否则，太好了
Otherwise, great
嗯，我认为这不足以伤害他
Well, I don't think it's enough to do him any harm
我可以帮他洗胃，但我想你不会为此感谢我的，是吗？
I could pump his stomach out, but I don't think you'd thank me for it, would you?
确保他有足够的水
Just make sure he has plenty of water
谢谢，说谢谢，帕特里克
Thanks. Say thank you, Patrick
谢谢你
Thank you
我的荣幸
My pleasure
行
Okay
用伤害打我
Hit me with the damage
他没有指控你
He hasn't charged you
你得让他知道帕特里克的近况
You've just gotta let him know how Patrick's doing
当你晚上有空吃饭的时候
and when you've got a night free for dinner
哦，正确
Oh. Right
嗯，这很奇怪
Well, that's strange
这不是我通常做生意的方式
It's not how I usually do business
那我付饭钱吗？这是怎么回事吗？
So do I pay for the meal? Is that how this works?
我不知道好吧，嗯，再见
I don't know Okay. Um, bye
好吧，再见，拜拜
Okay. Bye. Bye Bye
松饼大木头
Muffin Bigwood
- 这很酷  - 是啊
- That's cool.  - Yeah
然后他把它放在电脑上
And then he put it on the computer
并把它发给桌上的女孩
and sent it through to the girl on the desk
像小说里的东西
Like something out of a novel
哦，给你，叫我有点过时
Oh. There you go. Call me a little bit old-fashioned,
但是这不是最微小的令人毛骨悚然的吗？
but isn't that the tiniest bit creepy?
我总是在约会网站上遇到我的朋友
Well, I always meet mine off dating websites,
所以在我看来，这是比较明智的
so that seems relatively sane to me
啊，弗朗西斯小姐，兽医之旅怎么样？
Ah. Miss Francis, how did the trip to the vet go?
哦，比预期的要好，谢谢
Oh. Better than expected, thanks
你们这些女士觉得有什么好笑的？
What are you ladies finding so funny?
哦，没什么
Oh, nothing
奶油松饼？
Eclair?
不，谢谢你，莫林
No, thank you, Maureen
约翰？哦，谢谢你
John? Oh. Thank you
干得好
Well done
顺便说一句，弗朗西斯小姐
By the way, Miss Francis,
你知道你现在是唯一的员工吗
are you aware you are now the only member of staff
谁没有参加这场有趣的赛跑？
who is not taking part in the fun run?
什么？
What?
我担心菲利普斯太太会对我们的新老师持相当悲观的看法
I'm afraid Mrs. Phillips will take a rather dim view of our newest teacher
不参加学校活动
not partaking in school activities
呃，那就是你错的地方
Er, well, that's where you're wrong
莎拉今天早上报名参加了有趣的跑步
Sarah signed up to the fun run just this morning
是的，她代表她最喜欢的慈善机构参加竞选
Yes, she's running on behalf of her favorite charity
呃…呃帕格救援
Er... Er The Pug Rescue
社会嗯
Society Hmm
哦，好吧，那没关系
Oh. Well, that's all right, then
你做了什么？我跑不了五公里
What have you done? I can't run five kilometers
对不起，当他那样对我们大吼大叫的时候，我实在受不了
I'm sorry. I just can't bear it when he crows over us like that
哦，这太可怕了
Oh, this is awful
你在做吗，莫林？
Are you doing it, Maureen?
呃，我被豁免了，你怎么被豁免了？
Er, I'm exempt How are you exempt?
哮喘
Asthma
贝基，你为什么不能给我一些虚构的抱怨？
Becky, why couldn't you have given me some sort of fictional complaint?
对不起，这是我想到的第一件事
I'm sorry. It was the first thing that came to my head
你会再吃一杯吗？
Will you have another eclair?
是的，哦，我现在不行，我得跑五千米
Yeah. Oh. I can't now I've gotta run 5K
哦，继续，发生
Oh, go on. Go on
天堂
Heaven
第十一年补救措施在丘克斯的尝试我想我必须
Year 11 remedial's attempt at choux I think I'll have to
我不应该
I shouldn't
喔，我们开始吧
Whoo. Here we go
我不能这样做
I can't do this
我真的不能这样做，如果我必须跑去公共汽车，我会晕倒
I really can't do this. I faint if I have to run for the bus
很抱歉，但我想你必须这么做
Well, I'm sorry, but I think you're gonna have to
如果我这么做
If I'm doing this
你也在这么做
You're doing this too
来吧，弗朗西斯
Come on, Francis
我们不能去购物吗？贝基，你喜欢购物，是吗？
Can't we go shopping? You like shopping, don't you, Becky?
来吧，哦，我的上帝
Come on Oh, my God
喂，多宾，你能慢一分钟吗？
Oi, Dobbin, can you slow down for just a minute, please?
没有痛苦，就没有收获
No pain, no gain
我马上就要杀了你，我只是给你一个合理的警告
I'm gonna kill you in a minute I'm just giving you fair warning
哈，相信我，总有一天你会为此感谢我的
Ha. Trust me, you'll thank me for it one day
很多话浮现在脑海中，但感谢不在其中
A lot of words are coming to mind and thank ain't one of 'em
- 天啊  - 噢…
- Oh, God.  - Oh...
早上好莎拉
Morning, Sarah
早晨
Morning
所以，简正在为她的大喜日子做准备
So, Jane's getting ready for her big day
她买了裙子，蛋糕被预订了
She's got the dress, the cake's booked,
伴娘们都穿上了假衣服
the bridesmaids are all getting their fake tans
突然，一个家伙打破了聚会
And then suddenly, some bloke breaks up the party
宣布罗切斯特先生已经结婚
by announcing that Mr. Rochester is already married
情节扭曲，原来他妻子被锁在阁楼里，命运
Plot twist. Turns out his wife is locked up in the attic. Weird
罗切斯特先生说，对不起，我们不能成为夫妻
So Mr. Rochester says, Sorry, we can't be husband and wife
但是你作为一个非正式的罗切斯特太太继续呆下去怎么样？
But how about you stay on as a sort of unofficial Mrs. Rochester?
就像斯派克的爸爸
Like Spike's dad
哦，关闭
Oh. Shut up
简爱他，那么她做什么？
Jane loves him, so what does she do?
维克基？
Vikki?
简逃跑是因为她相信道德
Jane flees because she believes in a sense of morality
你知道，他已经发过誓了
You know, he's taken his vows
尽管这会让她心碎
and even though it would break her heart,
她不能和已婚男人勾搭上
she can't hook up with a married guy
那么为什么婚姻对简如此重要呢？
So why is marriage so important to Jane?
为什么她的原则比爱更重要？
Why are her principles more important than love?
婚姻为什么是一切？
Why is marriage everything?
不过，不是吗？没关系
Well, it's not, though, is it? It doesn't bloody matter
呃
Er
这不是你的错，小姐，我去接她
It's not your fault, miss I'll go fetch her
好吧，呃…我们继续呃，举起手来
Okay. Erm... We'll just carry on Er, hands up
帕特里克？举起手来？
Patrick? Hand up?
我们被驱逐了什么？
We're being evicted What?
我想他发现了温迪，我不敢相信
I think he's found out about Wendy I can't believe it
哦…哦，进来
Oh... Oh, come in
我无处可去
I've nowhere to go
我在这里已经多年了，我所有的朋友都在这里
I've been here for years All my friends are here
我该怎么办？
What am I going to do?
这是我们的错
This is our fault
我会告诉房东，讨厌的是帕特里克
I'll tell the landlord that it's Patrick who's the nuisance
那你和温迪就可以恢复正常了
Then you and Wendy can go back to normal
哦，谢谢你，莎拉
Oh, thank you, Sarah
无论如何，我很难找到他
I'm having trouble re-homing him anyway
没有人想要一只更老的狗，包括我
No one wants an older dog, including me
我们会找别的地方住
We'll find somewhere else to live
你要去哪里？
Where will you go?
嗯，总是有一个公园长椅
Well, there's always a park bench
非常喜欢那个公园
Getting quite fond of that park
哦，不
Oh, no
哦，我在开玩笑
Oh, I'm joking
哦
Oh
- 来吧  - 你好
- Come on.  - Hiya
你来还是去？
Are you coming or going?
哦，只是去
Oh. Just going
哦，不
Oh, no
哦，上帝
Oh, God
哦
Oh
上帝，如果这只狗出了问题，它会的
God, if it can go wrong with this dog, it will
哦，我有很多标记要做
Oh, I've got loads of marking to do
继续
Hold on
你们
You
啊
Ah
哦
Oh
这是你从一个虚度年华中得到的
This is what you get from a misspent youth
对不起，是我…它是开着的
Sorry. It's I've... It's open
啊，谢谢
Ah. Thanks
谢谢，不用担心
Thank you No worries
你觉得这有点太讲究了吗？
Do you think this is a bit too dressy?
不，我认为它真的适合你
No, I think it really suits you
我只是不想看起来我已经努力过了
I just don't wanna look like I've tried too hard
你为什么不试穿一下呢？让你看起来很时髦
Why don't you try that on with it? Make you look really funky
嗯，我想看起来时髦吗？
Hmm. Do I wanna look funky?
也许他更喜欢勤奋
Maybe he prefers studious
你有眼镜吗？不
Well, have you got any glasses? No
穿上夹克，好吗
Put the jacket on, then Okay
是的，是的，我喜欢
Yes. Yeah. I like
一只很酷的小鸡
One cool chick
你到底要去哪里？
Where are you going, anyway?
哦，桥边那个地方
Ooh, that place by the bridge
不错，他付钱吗？
Nice. Expensive Is he paying?
我真的希望如此，我现在正式无家可归
I really hope so. I'm now officially homeless,
因为帕特里克已经完成了他的使命
since Patrick has made it his mission
提醒房东不要养宠物
to alert the landlord to the no pets policy
你知道吗，我可以在这里帮你
Do you know, I might be able to help you here
真的吗？
Really?
我哥哥想在国外工作时出租他的房子
My brother wants to rent out his place while he's working abroad
他只需要支付费用，你有兴趣吗？
He only needs to cover the costs Are you interested?
有兴趣吗？
Interested?
太好了，是
Great. Yes
哦，这些？是的，把他们带上
Ooh. These? Yeah. Get 'em on
这些？
These ones?
嗨，这是一张两个人的桌子，我想是奥利弗的
Hi. It's a table for two I think it's under Oliver
是的
Yes Yeah
女士，请这边走，谢谢
Please, ma'am, this way Thank you
哦，我可以帮你拿外套吗
Oh, can I just take your coat
哦，不，对不起，这是事情的一部分，遗憾的
Oh, no. Sorry. It's part of the thing. Sorry
我的错误对不起，哎呦
My mistake Sorry. Whoops
谢谢这是你的桌子
Thanks Here is your table
谢谢你，我会回来的
Thank you I'll be back
遗憾的
Sorry
没关系
That's okay
老实说，我很抱歉
Honestly I'm sorry
不要，别担心，我一直在练习折纸
Don't. Don't worry. I've been practicing my origami
你的什么？
Your what?
没关系，你是在救人吗？
Never mind. Were you saving a life?
对不起？
Sorry?
你知道，给我拿一袋血浆，然后通过镊子
You know, get me a bag of plasma and pass the forceps
哦，不，我只是在看《权力的游戏》，忘记了时间
Oh, no. I was just watching Game of Thrones and lost track of time
嘿
Oh Hey
你选择了吗，先生？好的，请给我我平常的
Have you chosen, sir? Yeah, I'll have my usual, please
当然可以
Of course
哇，从来没有和一个以前有过老一套的人约会过
Wow. Never been out with a guy who has a usual before
你平时做什么？
What's your usual?
嗯，是丘拉斯科·德·洛莫，筹码的一面，被一个优秀的马尔贝克冲下来
Well, it's Churrasco de Lomo. Side of chips. Washed down by a good Malbec
嗯，听起来不错
Mmm. Sounds good
是的，我想吃牛排
Yeah. I was gonna have a steak
哦，这是牛排
Oh. It is a steak
哦，对了，请给我同样的
Oh, right. I'll have the same, please
稀有的
Rare, please
干得好
Well done
她也会有她的稀有的
She'll have hers rare as well
当然相信我
Of course Trust me
行
Okay
是的，我一直喜欢科学
Yeah, I've always loved the sciences
我在化学、生物和物理方面获得了A星
I got an A star in chemistry, biology and physics
真的可以做我想做的任何事情
Could have done anything I wanted to, really
但是我的父亲和兄弟是医生
But my father and brothers are doctors
他希望我也这样做
and he wanted me to do the same
是的，但是我背叛了，成为了一名兽医
Yeah, but I rebelled, became a vet
不过，这并不算什么反叛，是吗？我挣的比我哥哥多
Not much of a rebellion, though, is it? I earn more than my brother
但是，我们不做我们为钱做的事，是吗？
Well, we don't do what we do for the money, though, do we?
我们这样做是为了有所作为
We do it to make a difference
你知道你必须比医生多学习一年吗
Do you know you have to study a year longer than a doctor
因为你的病人不能告诉你哪里疼？
cause your patient can't tell you where it hurts?
提醒你，你有没有让杜宾犬把牙齿咬进你的胳膊里？
Mind you, have you ever had a Doberman sink its teeth into your arm?
嗯
Hmm
我想他想告诉我一些事情
I think he was trying to tell me something
不管怎样，关于我的事已经够多了，告诉我关于你的事
Anyway, enough about me Tell me about you
告诉我莎拉·弗朗西斯的事
Tell me about Sarah Francis
甜点吃什么？
Anything for dessert?
莎拉？布丁还是奶酪片？
Sarah? Pudding or slice of cheese?
不，不，我很好
No. No, I'm good
好吧，好吧，请给我们账单
Okay. Well, we'll have the bill, please
好吧，我会回来的谢谢
Okay. I'll be back Thank you
乐意平分吗？
Happy to go halves?
嗯…是
Mmm... Yeah
那我可以送你回家吗？
Then can I walk you home?
好的，谢谢
Okay, thanks
伟大的
Great
哦，你可以给你的病人一次检查
Oh. You could give your patient the once over
嗯，我有一个不成文的规则
Well, I kind of have this unwritten rule thing
我不免费看到约会对象的宠物
where I don't see my dates' pets for free,
不管这个女孩有多漂亮
no matter how pretty the girl is
啊
Ah
另一件我擅长的事是运动
The other thing I'm good at is sport
这种体格是完全自然的，我真的不需要努力
This physique is entirely natural I really don't have to work at it
哇，惊人的嗯
Wow. Amazing Mmm
奥利弗，我们能改天再喝咖啡吗？我只是有点累
Actually, Oliver, can we get coffee another time? I'm just a bit tired
你确定？
Are you sure?
是的，我度过了一个美好的夜晚，我只想回家
Yeah, and I've had a nice evening I just wanna go home
那么，你下周的工作安排如何？
Well, how are you fixed for next week?
啊…我不确定我是否有点忙
Ah... I'm not sure I'm a bit busy
有…我做错什么了吗？
Have... Have I done something wrong?
呃…真相？
Er... The truth?
说真的，你…你不想再见到我吗？
Seriously, you... You don't wanna see me again?
不
No
好吧，你约我出去，呃，你迟到了
Okay, you asked me out, er, you were late,
我是说，晚了，然后你不停地谈论自己
and, I mean, late, and then you talked nonstop about yourself
然后当我冒昧地暗示你可能会想要
and then when I had the temerity to suggest that you might wanna take
偷看一下你的病人，你说这违反了规定
a peek at your patient, you said it's against the rules
但是牛排很好吃，不是吗？
But the steak was good, wasn't it?
为什么要回家去一个空公寓？
And why go home to an empty flat?
谢谢你，奥利弗，但是不，谢谢你
Thanks, Oliver, but no thanks
哦，嗯，为了你的信息
Oh, and, um, for your information,
我不会回到一个空公寓
I'm not going home to an empty flat
哦，你好
Oh, hello
嗨，你一个人在外面干什么？
Hi. What are you doing out here on your own?
马歇尔·克洛斯，麦克斯
Marshall Close. Max.
哦，我知道你住在哪里
Oh, I know where you live
我们去看看是否有人在家好吗？
Shall we go and see if anyone's at home?
是吗？好吧，来吧
Yeah? Okay, come on
来吧，好孩子，开始
Come on Good boy. Come on
什么？嗯？
What? Eh?
喂？
Hello?
你好，孩子，你去哪儿了？
Hello, boy Where have you been?
我希望你能…对不起，门开着
I wish you could... Sorry The door was open
你好
Hi
哦，你忘了回家的路，是吗？
Oh. You forgot your way home, did you?
哦！看起来很恶心
Ooh! That looks nasty
你越来越像我了
You're getting just like me
我检查了我能想到的所有地方，尽管愚蠢的是
I've checked everywhere I can think of, although, stupidly,
忘了检查一下
forgot to check just there
在这里干吗？
What are you doing here?
哦，我认识艾伯特很多年了
Oh, I've known Albert for years
是的，如果不是本
Yeah. If it wasn't for Ben,
我应该还躺在那条小路上
I should still be lying on that towpath
你摔倒了吗？
Did you have a fall?
不，不，我通常头上戴着鱼手指四处走动，本
No, no, I usually walk about with fish fingers on me head. Ben,
把它们放在冰箱里，好吗？明天我要给我喝茶
stick 'em in the freezer, will you? I'll have 'em for me tea tomorrow
好孩子好孩子，你坐
Good boy Good boy. You sit
你让我担心生病了，你担心了，我不知道你去了哪里
You had me worried sick, you did I didn't know where you'd gone
巧克力消化液不会出错！
And a chocolate digestive wouldn't go amiss!
称自己为救援委员会？嗯
Call yourselves a rescue committee? Huh
不客气
You're welcome
一定是昏过去了
Must have blacked out
顽固的老家伙拒绝去医院
Stubborn old bugger refuses to go to the hospital
你看起来不错
You look nice
和女孩出去过夜？
Night out with the girls?
不，我希望
No. I wish
我想他给了自己很大的惊吓
I think he's given himself quite a scare
最糟糕的是失去了马克斯
Worst part was losing Max
嗯
Hmm
你玩得开心吗？
Did you have a nice time?
不见得
Not really
我一直告诉他，他需要给自己弄辆摩托车
I keep telling him he needs to get himself a scooter
我买不起
I can't afford one
至少他的听力没有问题
At least there's nothing wrong with his hearing
他妻子在哪里？
Where's his wife?
呃，她去年去世了
Er, she died last year
嗯
Hmm
结婚五十年了哇
Been married 50 years Wow
五十年了，不要以为我会持续一个周末
Fifty years. Don't think I'd last a weekend
燃烧的茶在哪里？
Where's the flaming tea?
让这一天成为一天，嗯
Make that a day Hmm
遗憾的
Sorry
你真的想在开始之前伸展肌肉，好吗？
You really wanna stretch out the muscles before you start, all right?
否则，你最终会拉什么东西
Otherwise, you'll end up pulling something
林前，说到哪
Cor, talking of which
你好你好
Hello Hello
过得愉快
Have a nice day
哦
Oh
我通常不会这么快就把它们推迟
I don't usually put them off that quickly
他们通常非常热衷，直到他们看到我的毛绒玩具收藏
They're usually quite keen until they see my soft toy collection
不，不是你，是我，是兽医
No, it wasn't you. It was me That was the vet
什么？
What?
哦，你的钱包掉了
Oh. You've dropped your wallet
好吧，来吧，这不会让你为五千米做好准备
Right, come on. This isn't gonna get you ready for the 5K
弗朗西斯，站起来
On your feet, Francis
开始
Come on
嗯？
Well?
你怎么想呢？
What do you think?
嗯？
Huh?
一百万年内不会
Not in a million years
我想我会走五公里吗
am I ever gonna make five kilometers is what I think
没有
No. Of this
这是我哥哥的
Well, it's my brother's,
他离开工作至少两年了
and he's away working for at least two years,
我认为这对你和帕特里克来说是完美的
and I thought it would be perfect for you and Patrick
没那么贵
It's not that expensive. I
我想那会很好
I thought it'd be nice
哦
Oh
哦，贝基
Oh, Becky
贝基，太棒了
Becky, it's wonderful
哦，谢谢你
Oh, thank you
谢谢你，我爱它，我只是爱它
Thank you. I love it I just love it
不客气哦！
You're welcome Oh!
哦，我的上帝哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God Oh, my God
天啊，看
Oh, my gosh. Look
哦，帕特里克，看看它
Oh, Patrick, look at it
- 伙计们，来吧，说真的  - 我正在转动它
- Guys, come on. Seriously.  - I am turning it.
- 你带错工具了  - 好吧
- You've brought the wrong tools.  - Okay.
这是怎么回事？
What is going on here?
没什么
Nothing Nothing
啊，对我来说这不像什么
Ah. It doesn't look like nothing to me
这是我爸爸的车它需要，呃
This is my dad's car It needs, erm
新轮胎，它需要新轮胎，新车轮
New tires. It needs New tires, new wheels
很有趣，因为我在这附近什么地方都没看见你爸爸
It's funny, 'cause I don't see your dad anywhere 'round here
但是别担心，我得走了
But don't worry, I've gotta go
我会的…我一进学校就给你爸爸打电话
I'll... I'll call your dad when I get into school
你不需要给任何人打电话请不要给任何人打电话
You don't need to call anyone Please, don't call anyone
不？不
No? No
不不
No No
所以我再次问你们，先生们，这是怎么回事？
So I ask you again, gentlemen, what is going on here?
小姐，我们在偷车轮
We're stealing the wheels, miss
我还能说什么？
What else am I gonna say?
你怎么知道怎么做这种事？
How do you even know how to do something like that?
看了几段视频是的
Watched a couple of videos Yeah
他哥哥给他看了
His brother showed him Yeah
对，你哥哥在哪里？
Right, where's your brother?
- 没关系  - 他在少管所，小姐
- Doesn't matter.  - He's in juvie, miss.
啊，闭嘴，斯派克，对不起
Ah. Shut up, Spike I'm sorry
对不起，伙计
Sorry, man
好吧，听着，我不会告诉任何人这件事
Okay, look, I'm not gonna tell anyone about this,
好吗？但是如果我再次听到或看到你们中的任何人做这样的事情
okay? But if I hear or catch any of you doing something like this again,
我很乐意报警
I will happily call the police
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，你要去哪里？
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa Where are you going?
对不起，你不能逍遥法外
Sorry. You're not getting away with this scot-free
小姐，我必须去
Miss, I've got to
这将是我本周第三次被拘留，我会惹上这么多麻烦
It'll be my third detention this week. I'll get in so much trouble
哦，不，不，这比拘留更糟糕，斯派克，好吗？
Ooh, no, no. It's way worse than detention, Spike, okay?
这是弗朗西斯小姐社区服务，好吗？
This is the Miss Francis community service, okay?
你们都要报名参加有趣的跑步
You are all gonna sign up for the fun run
小姐！得到二十英镑的赞助
Aw, miss! And get ￡20 sponsorship
没有争论，和…你现在就要开始训练了
No arguments. And... And you're gonna start your training now
怎么做？
How?
你可以跟着跑
You can run along
继续，他们必须被吃掉
Go on. They've got to be eaten
事实上他们一定是
They've actually got to be
莫林，这些纸杯蛋糕真漂亮
Maureen, these cupcakes are gorgeous
它们不好吃吗？是的，我知道
Aren't they good? Yes, I know
让我试试呃，不
Let me try one Er, no
直到你跑完了
Not until you've finished the run
啊，太不公平了，不
Ah, that's so unfair No
纸杯蛋糕？
Cupcake?
谢谢你
Thank you
哦，这不是一个爱的术语，我给你一个纸杯蛋糕
Oh, it's not a term of endearment I'm offering you a cupcake
不，谢谢你，莫林
No, thank you, Maureen
我和我的班级要去公园慢跑，为跑步做准备
My class and I are off for a jog in the park in preparation for the run
校长对投票率印象非常深刻
Head teacher's very impressed with the turnout
弗朗西斯小姐，真遗憾你的班级没有这么热心
Such a shame your class aren't as keen, Miss Francis
啊，好吧，那就是你错的地方，彼得斯先生
Ah, well, that's where you're wrong, Mr. Peters
我班上所有的男生
All the boys in my class
现在已经签约了，一些女孩也表现出了兴趣
have now signed up and some of the girls are showing interest too
你到底用什么威胁他们？没有任何东西
What on Earth did you threaten them with? Nothing
他们这么做是因为他们想成为我的朋友
They're doing it 'cause they want to be my friends
你要小心，你知道吗
You want to be careful, you know
我听说菲利普斯退休时，他是校长的下一个接班人
I hear he's next in line for the headmaster when Phillips retires
很抱歉，是他先开始的
Well, I'm sorry He started it
是的，但是我们希望你留下来
Yeah But we want you to stay
是的，我们有，我们有，我也有
Yes, we do, we do So do I
纸杯蛋糕
Cupcake
不，莫琳，住手
No. Maureen, stop it
为什么我的东西必须储存起来？
Why is it my stuff that had to go into storage?
嗯？
Hmm?
那么维多利亚时代的英格兰是什么
So what is it about Victorian England
这让罗切斯特太太对社会如此不可接受？
that makes Mrs. Rochester so unacceptable to society?
是吗？
Yes?
来吧，你这个懒鬼！
Come on, you lazy Oops!
莎拉？
Sarah?
不
No
等待
Wait
不，哦，我的上帝
No. Oh, my God
哦，我的上帝，太可爱了
Oh, my God It's so cute
进来，进来吧
Come in. Come in There you go
谢谢你，谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you
我是买了一个还是只买了一个
Do I get one of these or is it just
不，恐怕你冒着生命危险
No, you risk your life, I'm afraid
我注定要淹死
I'm destined to drown
卡莉·威廉姆斯？
Carly Williams?
礼物
Present
迈克尔·阿齐基瓦？
Michael Azikiwe?
是
Yeah
维克·安德鲁斯？
Vikki Andrews?
维克基？
Vikki?
有人知道维克在哪里吗？
Does anyone know where Vikki is?
开始
Come on
吐出来，午饭前我们有一个英语普通中等教育证书要完成
Spit it out. We've got an English GCSE to accomplish by lunchtime
嗯，维克基的父母一直有问题
Erm, Vikki's mum and dad have been having problems
她并没有真正处理这件事
She's not really handling it
塔里克，那是私人恩怨
Tariq, that's private
遗憾的
Sorry
她有麻烦吗，小姐？
Is she in trouble, miss?
如果我能帮得上忙就不行了
Not if I can help it
呃，我的奶奶膝盖不舒服
Er, my nan's got dodgy knees
我在想，我也可以被原谅吗？
I was wondering, can I be excused too?
不错的尝试，好，把你的文件翻过来
Nice try. Right, turn over your papers
你有九十分钟，开始
You have 90 minutes. Begin
嘿，我是维克基
Hey, it's Vikki
请留言，我会给你回电话
Leave a message and I'll call you back
你好
Hello Hi
我是弗朗西斯小姐，维克基的英语老师
I'm Miss Francis, Vikki's English teacher
听着，我今天早上想让她参加考试
Look, I tried to get her to that exam this morning
我告诉她这有多重要
I tell her how important it is
但是我们正在经历一些家庭问题
But we're going through a few family problems
嗯，听到这个消息我很难过
Hmm. I'm so sorry to hear that
哦，我丈夫和我要分手了
Oh. My husband and I are splitting up
你只是喜欢告诉别人，不是吗？
You just love telling people, don't you?
她，嗯，接受得很糟糕
She's, um, taking it quite badly
我的
My
我有麻烦了吗？
Am I in trouble?
不是和我一起，你想和我们一起去散步吗？
Not with me. Do you wanna come for a walk with us?
是啊，我去拿我的外套
Yeah, I'll just grab my coat
哦，我看她问你时你会做些什么
Oh. I see you'll do something when she asks
是的，她很好地问我
Yeah. She asks me nicely
啊
Ah
看到我反对什么了吗？
See what I'm up against?
她决定了
And she's decided
她不想来和我和我男朋友住在一起
she doesn't want to come and live with me and my boyfriend
她想留下来
She wants to stay
和她爸爸在一起
With her dad
哦
Oh
我们马上回来
We'll be right back
行
Okay
听着，我真的很抱歉
Look, I'm really sorry
维克基，你擅长英语，好吗？最好的之一
Vikki, you're good at English, okay? One of the best
我为你预测一个七，没问题
I predict a seven for you, no problem
但是你必须做的一件事是去参加考试
But the one thing you have to do is turn up for the exam
这只是家里的事情
It's just this whole thing at home
我一直感觉很糟糕
I feel so crap all the time
我没有去，因为我不想搞砸
I didn't go 'cause I don't wanna mess up
好吧，我能告诉你一些你必须保密的事情吗？
Okay. Can I tell you something you must keep to yourself?
是的，反正没人听我的
Yeah. No one listens to me anyway
好吧，我有一个姐姐
Okay, well, I have an older sister
我一直生活在她的阴影中
and I have always lived in her shadow
你知道，她什么都有
You know, she's got everything,
她实现了一切
she's achieved everything
我妈妈总是让我知道这件事
My mum never fails to let me know it
但是我奶奶给了我一个很好的建议
But my granny gave me a really good bit of advice
她说，只要把一只脚放在另一只脚前面
She said, Just keep putting one foot in front of the other,
最后，感觉就像走路一样
and in the end, it feels like walking.
所以我已经安排你这个星期六来坐你的英文报纸
So I've arranged for you to come in this Saturday and sit your English paper
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
你为我做的？
You've done that for me?
当然，你不能和任何人讨论你的论文
Of course. You mustn't discuss your paper with anyone else
明白吗？
Understood?
我会知道你以前是否见过这些问题，好吗？我很奇怪
I will know if you've seen the questions before, okay? I'm weird like that
我发誓，穿过我的心，希望死去
I absolutely swear. Cross my heart and hope to die
不要走那么远
Don't go that far
好吧，我们应该把你带回来
Right, we should get you back
那么，来吧
Come on, then
这个星期六你没有任何计划，是吗？
You didn't have any plans this Saturday, did you?
不，我什么都不做
No, I never do anything
喂？
Hello?
你好，莎拉？
Hello. Sarah?
本？
Ben?
是你吗？
Is that you?
我又失望了
I disappoint again
和平提议？
Peace offering?
开始
Come on
那么，是什么让你来到了威兰德利亚的船民？
So, what brings you to the Boat People of Wetlandia?
我来是因为我一直在想你那天晚上说的话
I came because I've been thinking about what you said the other night
我听说你跑得很开心
And I hear you're doing a fun run
啊，嗯，你说得对一半，我正在跑步
Ah. Well, you're half right I am running
那太好了，我很愿意赞助你
That's great I'd love to sponsor you
我认为你这样做是有原因的？
I take it you're doing it for a good cause?
也许是社会不健全的兽医的康复？
Maybe the rehabilitation of hopelessly socially inadequate vets?
像这样的事情
Something like that
当然，嗯，你几乎可以保证不用付钱
Of course, um, you're almost guaranteed not to have to pay
因为我完成五千米的可能性非常小
as the likelihood of me finishing 5K is pretty slim
行
Okay
哦！
Oh!
哇，你确定？这很慷慨
Wow. Are you sure? That is very generous
那是我
That's me
不足但慷慨
Inadequate but generous
我现在真的要这么做了，不是吗？
I'm really gonna have to do this now, aren't I?
害怕如此
Afraid so
呃，我第一个学期就活了下来
Ugh. I've survived my first term
你已经活下来了，你已经有所作为了
You've more than survived You've made a difference
对谁？给孩子们
To who? To the kids
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
哦，莫林
Oh. Maureen
你要去哪里？
Are you going on somewhere?
啊…哦，不，不，有人告诉我这是一件漂亮的衣服
Eh... Oh. No, no. Someone told me it was fancy dress
我觉得你看起来很棒
Well, I think you look fabulous
我知道
I know
恭喜你，弗朗西斯小姐
Congratulations, Miss Francis
你没有我预测的那么糟糕
You're not doing as badly as I predicted you would
哦，我被微弱的赞美所诅咒谢谢你，彼得斯先生
Oh. I feel damned by faint praise Thank you, Mr. Peters
我想
I think
你准备好参加五千米赛跑了吗？
Are you ready for the 5K run?
到达那里
Getting there
你不是真的在参加帕格救援队吧？
You're not really running for the Pug Rescue, are you?
嗯，一只狗和它有关系
Well, a dog's got something to do with it
聪明的屁股
Wise arse
我听说了
I heard that
是啊，你是命中注定的
Yeah, you were meant to
正确
Right
五，六，一失踪
Five, six One missing
帕特里克！
Patrick!
帕特里克？
Patrick?
帕特里克，你在哪里？
Patrick, where are you?
帕特里克？
Patrick?
帕特里克！
Patrick!
嗯，他有微缺口吗？
Well, is he micro-chipped?
我不知道
I don't know
哦，听着，我肯定我们会找到他的
Oh, look, I'm sure we're gonna find him
你到底基于什么？
What are you basing that on exactly?
他真是个可爱的小伙子
Well, he's such a lovely chap
听着，我们为什么不分开
Look, why don't we split up,
然后我们会在这里汇报
and then we'll report back here
对，行
Right. Okay
我会得到更多的帮助对吧，所以
I'll get more help Right, so
哦，对不起，对不起，那是我的
Oh, sorry, sorry That was my
对不起，我很抱歉蛋糕！
Sorry. I'm so sorry The cakes!
我要去普拉提
I'm off to Pilates
哦，你好
Oh. Hi
莎拉，你到处走走
Sarah You get around
是谁呀？
Who is it?
哦，我在找维克基
Oh, I was looking for Vikki
她在楼上
She's upstairs
你好，弗朗西斯小姐，我会帮你找她
Hello, Miss Francis I'll get her for you
这是本，我丈夫
This is Ben, my husband
我本来想告诉你哦
I was gonna tell you Oh
弗朗西斯小姐在楼下
Miss Francis is downstairs
呃，不，我的意思是，为什么你要告诉我？
Er, no. I mean, why Why would you tell me?
那绝对好
That's absolutely fine
好吧，你是维克基的爸爸，我应该知道的
Okay, you're Vikki's dad I should have known that
嘿，弗朗西斯小姐
Hey, Miss Francis
怎么了？
What's up?
嗨，呃，我失去了帕特里克
Hi. Erm I've lost Patrick
我想知道你能否帮我找到他
I was wondering if you could help me find him,
如果你不太忙，我当然会去拿外套
if you're not too busy. Of course I'll go and get my coat
我能帮忙吗？不！我是说
Can I help? No! I mean,
不，没事，我们会没事的
no, it's fine We'll be fine
所以，我会再见你的
So, I'll see you around
我们去找帕特里克吧
Let's go and find Patrick
我本来想告诉你的
I was gonna tell you
哦，不，老实说，请你为什么要告诉我？
Oh. No, honestly, please Why would you tell me?
这很奇怪，如果有的话
That's weird, if anything,
如果你告诉我
if you'd told me
再见，我的意思是，这甚至不是一件事
Bye. I mean, it's not even a thing
为什么你会认为这是一件事，而不是一件事？
Why would you think it's a thing when it's not even a thing?
我的意思是，停止自言自语你听起来完全疯了
I mean, stop talking to yourself You sound completely mad
对不起？没有任何东西
Sorry? Nothing
哦，奶奶，我很抱歉
Oh, Granny, I'm so sorry
莎拉，你做了什么？
Sarah, what have you done?
生日快乐，爸爸
Happy birthday, Dad
那里，那里，布丁
There, there, pudding
他会出现的
He'll turn up
开始
Come on
不要告诉卡罗琳我哭了
Don't tell Caroline I cried
不，当然不是
No, of course not
太妃糖布丁？他们是你最喜欢的
Toffee, pudding? They're your favorite
哦，我不会的
Oh. I won't
我明天应该跑五公里
I'm supposed to be running five kilometers tomorrow
为什么？你偷了什么东西吗？
Why? Have you stolen something?
老实说，无论如何，我都不想这么做
To be honest, I don't feel much like doing it anyway
为什么？
Why?
我想念帕特里克
I'm missing Patrick
莎拉
Oh, Sarah
他咕哝和打鼾，但他在我身上渐渐长大
He grunts and snores, but he's kind of growing on me
我也有魔法
I have that magic too
听起来和我很般配
Sounds like a perfect match to me
闭嘴，老实说，你失去了他，我并不感到惊讶
Oh, shut up. Honestly, I'm not surprised you lost him
啊，现在，这不公平
Ah, now, that's not fair
不，莎拉非常努力
No. Sarah tries very hard
是的，有一天她会成功的
Yes, and one day she's going to succeed
对不起，请你们都别这么屈尊俯就好吗？
Sorry, can you all stop being so patronizing, please?
爸爸，有什么喝的吗？
Dad, is there anything to drink?
当然，布丁你想要什么？
Of course, pudding What would you like?
一品脱玻璃杯里的任何东西，请
Anything that comes in a pint glass. Please
杜松子酒和滋补品听起来不错
Gin and tonic Sounds great
第二个想法，拿着补药
Second thoughts, hold the tonic
我以为你明天会跑得很开心
I thought you were meant to be doing a fun run tomorrow
现在，如果你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要去厨房庆祝我爸爸的生日
I'm going to the kitchen to celebrate my dad's birthday
老实说，你不能对她说什么她太敏感了
Honestly, you can't say anything to her She's so sensitive
什么？
What?
哦，谢谢你
Aw. Thank you
哦
Oh
莎拉？喂？
Sarah? Hello?
我是本
It's Ben
对，谁给爸爸的煎饼？
Right, who's for Daddy's pancakes?
我，我，我哦，是的，求你了，爸爸
Me, me, me Ooh, yes, please, Daddy
为什么没人叫醒我？
Why did no one wake me?
我要迟到了，因为我有赞助商和一切
I'm gonna be late for my run I've got sponsors and everything
我是赞助商，我不介意
I'm a sponsor and I don't mind
你需要睡觉，亲爱的
You needed your sleep, darling
哦，这对我很重要
Oh. This is important to me
你确定杜松子酒不在你的系统里吗？
Are you sure that gin's out of your system?
你能说点什么帮助你一生中的一次吗？
Could you say something helpful for just once in your life?
什么？我做了什么？
What? What have I done?
什么？什么？
What? What?
有人死于事故吗？
Has someone died in an accident?
奇怪，好吧，来吧，哦，上帝
Weird. Okay Come on. Oh, God
哦
Oh
我真的会筋疲力尽的
I am actually gonna be exhausted
在这场愚蠢的比赛开始之前
before this stupid race even starts
啊…不！
Ah... No!
你错过了他们二十分钟前离开的
You've missed it They left 20 minutes ago
老实说
Honestly,
我不能得到任何正确的东西，我完全没有用
I can't get anything right I am utterly useless
你为什么不跑？
Well, why aren't you running?
拉伤腿筋
Pulled a hamstring
典型的
Typical
在对我大吼大叫之后，你连跑步都没有
After all that crowing over me and you're not even running
不
No
我们需要把这些放进车里
We need to get these in the cars
我的赞助会让一个老人非常开心
My sponsorship was gonna make an old man very happy,
或者至少不那么悲惨
or at least a bit less miserable
哦，老实说，我会哭的
Oh, honestly, I could weep
弗朗西斯小姐
Miss Francis
莎拉
Sarah
我可以担保你开始
I could vouch for you starting
我是菲利普斯太太的副手
I am Mrs. Phillips' deputy
哦，谢谢你，呃
Oh, thank you. Erm
游隼
Peregrine
像猎鹰一样？
Like the falcon?
是
Yes
谢谢你，呃，佩里格林
Thank you, er, Peregrine
请回到队伍后面
Back behind the line, please
好像这将会改变五公里的距离
As if that's gonna make a difference over five kilometers
好吧，我们还是好好做吧
Well, we might as well do it properly
三个
Three,
二，一，哇！
two, one. Waah!
那是什么？
What was that?
菲利普斯太太喝了一瓶可乐
Mrs. Phillips had a klaxon
行
Okay
让我们做这件事
Let's do this thing
行
Okay
过来，狗狗
Come here, doggy
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
你确定你没事吗？
Are you sure you're okay?
是的，是的，我很好
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine
我可以做个安全记录吗？
Could I just make a safety note?
请不要靠在障碍物上
Please do not lean on the barriers
我们今天发生了一些事件
We have had a number of incidents today
我们也有很多
And we also do have a lot
继续，米奇，发生
Go on, Mikey. Go on
获胜者是迈克尔·阿齐基瓦
And the winner is Michael Azikiwe
我为你感到骄傲
I am so proud of you
干得好你真的做到了
Well done You've actually done it
可怕的
Awesome
哦，干得好，迈克尔，恭喜
Oh, well done, Michael. Congratulations
哦，我不知道你是个跑步者
Oh, I didn't know you were a runner
你为什么不告诉我你可以这样跑？
Why didn't you tell me you could run like that?
我不知道，弗朗西斯小姐让我做的
I don't know. Miss Francis made me do it
你一定要感谢弗朗西斯小姐
Well, you make sure you thank Miss Francis
你有天赋
You've got talent
我们取消了
We have canceled
恐怕是海绵老师游戏
the sponge-a-teacher game I'm afraid
如果人们能多一点
If people could be a little more
维克基！维克基！
Vikki! Vikki!
嘿！嘿！嘿！
Hey-hey-Hey!
你做到了，亲爱的
You did it, darling
干得好
Well done
谢谢，爸爸
Thanks, Dad
很抱歉，我最近一直很困难
I'm sorry I've been so difficult recently
哦…别担心
Oh... Don't worry
这对我们所有人来说都很难
It's been hard on all of us
现在妈妈走了会更容易
It'll be easier now Mum's gone
这对她更好
It's better for her
你和我，我们会处理得很好
And you and me, we'll manage just fine
你好
Hi
嗨
Oh, hi
有点晚了，不是吗？
Little bit late, aren't we?
不，只是明年初
No, just early for next year
如果你愿意，我可以和你一起跑一会儿
I can run with you for a bit if you like
减轻找个人谈话的痛苦
Eases the pain to have someone to talk to
哦…我不能
Oh... I can't
肖小姐！
Miss Shaw!
是的，菲利普斯太太？
Yes, Mrs. Phillips?
我只是…哦
I've just... Oh
我刚收到彼得斯先生的留言
I've, erm, I've just had a message from Mr. Peters
弗朗西斯小姐正在跑步
Miss Francis is running
她迟到了，但她确实开始了
She was late, but she did start
聪明的
Brilliant
我能借你的扬声器吗？
Can I borrow your loudhailer?
我只是想
I'm just gonna
仅仅…我要去拿
Just... I'm just gonna take
莫林可爱的巴普
Maureen Lovely baps
谢谢你
Thank you
我想你是从这里得到的
I think you've got it from here
朋友？
Friends?
朋友
Friends
大家听好了
Listen up, everybody
我的朋友莎拉开始了比赛
My friend Sarah started the race
她筹集了一千英镑的赞助，为一位老人买了一辆机动滑板车
She's raised sponsorship of ￡1,000 to buy an old man a mobility scooter
如果有人能抽出一点时间
If anyone could just spare a little bit of time
为了让她回家高兴，请留下来
to cheer her home, please stay
请
Please
不要离开拜托，来吧
Don't leave Please, come on
哦，哦！
Oh, ooh!
哦，不，我想她不会来了
Oh, no. I don't think she's coming
她会有信心的
She will Have some faith
哦，上帝
Oh, God
如果她有什么感觉
If she had any sense,
她会停下来喝杯咖啡和一块蛋糕
she'd have stopped for a cup of coffee and a cake
弗朗西斯小姐！弗朗西斯小姐！
Miss Francis! Miss Francis!
来吧，莎拉，你能行，开始
Come on, Sarah You can do it. Come on
来吧，莎拉，继续前进，发生
Come on, Sarah, keep going Keep going. Go on
弗朗西斯小姐！弗朗西斯小姐！
Miss Francis! Miss Francis!
哦，来吧，莎拉，你能行
Oh. Come on, Sarah You can do it
弗朗西斯小姐！弗朗西斯小姐！
Miss Francis! Miss Francis!
小姐，小姐，不，来吧，你能行
Miss, miss, no Come on, you can do it
帕特里克？
Patrick?
弗朗西斯小姐！弗朗西斯小姐！
Miss Francis! Miss Francis!
干得好，干得好
Well done. Well done
太棒了，干得好
Bravo. Well done
是的！
Yes!
世界卫生大会
Wha
我没死
I'm not dead
哦，帕特里克
Aw. Patrick
我的帕特里克
My Patrick
你通过了，你们都通过了
You passed. You all flipping passed
我得了五分，我得了四分，小姐
And I got a five And I got a four, miss
我甚至得到了一个三分
And I even I got a three
斯派克，是啊，是啊，没关系，只有三个
Spike. Yeah, yeah, it's all right It's only a three
我得了八分，谢谢你的一切
I got an eight Thank you for everything
随时
Any time
- 好啦  - 嗨，艾伯特
- There.  - Hi, Albert.
新的机动滑板车怎么样？
How's the new mobility scooter?
是啊，是啊，不错，是啊，你好
Yeah, yeah, not bad, yeah Hello
是的，可惜他们没有绿色的，是
Yeah, it's a shame they didn't have it in green. Yeah
听着
Here, listen,
呃，当你跑完之后，如果你想喝杯茶
er, when you finish your run, if you fancy a cup of tea,
你知道我们在哪里哦，我很乐意
you know where we are Oh, I'd love to
带些饼干就行了
Bring some biscuits Will do
呃，把他也带来
And, er, bring him as well
好吧，塔塔塔
All right Ta-ta
再见
See you
那么，来吧
Come on, then
嘿！
Hey!
饿吗？
Hungry?
谁是妈妈的特别男孩？
Who's Mummy's special boy?
是的，开始
Yeah. Come on
帕特里克来集合
Patrick to set
有人见过帕特里克吗？
Has anyone seen Patrick?